{
    "id": "8ceff0513b7a43408329b7429c9b6c1e",
    "title": "Few, Little, The Few, The Little",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "…………………. children participated in the program.",
            "description": "We use few with countable nouns and little with uncountable nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "A little",
                "Few",
                "Little"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a49baf25fec04b4fab7661ff41980195"
        },
        {
            "question": "There is ………………… water in the well.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "few"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fed105c306704faba48a3a74b320bfc7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The average MP has ………………….. real power.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "few"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "18cae1e5d6ee4a6486547bfb44083eb2"
        },
        {
            "question": "His ideas are difficult. ………………… people can understand them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Few",
                "Little"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "96296529d9664fe987491f54490dc491"
        },
        {
            "question": "We have gotten a ..................... meat and a ………………….. eggs.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "little, few",
                "few, little",
                "few, few",
                "little, little"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3208dbfdfe3c45959bb431dd40116124"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can I try ………………….. of your soup?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "a little",
                "few",
                "a few"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f7c24953471743999ba1f1cf5413d69d"
        },
        {
            "question": "In spite of being the daughter of a politician, she has ………………… interest in politics.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "little",
                "a few",
                "a little"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "db8c86c7cd0d44049ee68441377db296"
        },
        {
            "question": "Money is of ………………….. consequence.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "little",
                "a little"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3f954043c22a4b2eafdd5cbb5c94caf6"
        },
        {
            "question": "We were given ………………. work today than yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "little",
                "fewer"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6b9d8f64b9ad45be9f985ddcc1f5c32d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He earns ……………….. money than his wife.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "less",
                "little",
                "few"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cd1f5f68e68c4b299af1d4a652ae4b6a"
        }
    ]
}